Olga Molchanova

Junior Full Stack Developer

PROFILE

I am an experienced Real Estate Agent with a passion for helping clients find their dream homes. I have extensive experience in the industry, including more than 5 years working as a real estate agent. I am knowledgeable about the latest market trends and understand the nuances of the real estate market. I pride myself on my ability to negotiate the best deals for my clients and to navigate complex real estate agreements. I am highly organized, detail-oriented, and have strong communication skills.

+38(096)89-05-772 designer.molchanova@gmail.com

Kyiv City, Ukraine
linkedin.com
github.com
mysite.com

TECH SKILLS

Programming Languages JavaScript (ES6), HTML, CSS

Web Technologies & Tools React, Node.js, React Native, VS Code, Git, GitHub, Vite, Sass, Figma

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior chemist chromatographer

Vitamin Plant of Kyiv

2016 - present

- Working with documentation, including foreign sources
- Planning, research and development of drug analysis methods
- Training of junior specialists
- Compliance with deadlines
- Teamwork skills

Laboratory assistant

Pharmaceutical Company Darnytsia

2015 - 2016

- Working width a PC and specific software
- Working with reagents, laboratory equipment and instruments

Cashier seller in the supermarket

2014 - 2015

• Communication skills width customers

EDUCATION

IT School GoIT

2023 - 2024

Fullstack Developer

Taras Shevchenko National University of Kyiv

2009 - 2015

Master's degree

Chemist, scientist

LENGUAGES

- English Pre-Intermediate
- Ukrainian Native